♪ In the not
too distant future ♪
♪ somewhere in time
and space ♪
♪ mike nelson
and his robot pals ♪
♪ are caught
in a nasty place ♪
♪ they try to survive
the wrath of pearl ♪
♪ just an evil gal
who wants to rule the world ♪
♪ from her castle below
she sets her sights above ♪
♪ just to torture
all her captives ♪
♪ on the satellite above ♪
Get me down!
♪ I’ll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst I can find ♪
♪ la la la ♪
♪ he’ll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and i’ll monitor
his mind ♪
♪ la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
mike can’t control ♪
♪ where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ la la la ♪
♪ he’ll try to keep
his sanity ♪
♪ with the help
of his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call.
Cambot "you’re on"
gypsy "oh my stars"
tom servo "check me out"
croooow "i’m different"
♪ if you’re wonderin’
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other
science facts ♪
♪ la la la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself,
"it’s just a show ♪
♪ "I should really just relax ♪
♪ for mystery science
theater 3000" ♪
Okay, 26 columns.
Enter.
Hi, everyone.
Welcome to the s.O.L.
Lately, gypsy’s been wondering
if she’s once, twice,
maybe even three times
a lady.
As a woman,
i’m naturally curious.
Right, so crow here came up
with a spreadsheet program
that’ll answer
that very question.
Okay, uh, using
senator diane feinstein
as a baseline...
Since she is exactly
one time a lady...
Right.
We enter "gypsy" there,
and the answer is...
- You’re 2.7 times a lady.
- Aw.
No, well that’s not bad.
Sure,
winona is 3.3 times a lady,
but nina totenberg
is only 2 1/2.
And melissa etheridge
is, ooh, well, pretty low.
Gillian anderson herself
is only a 2.9.
Wow!
Yeah.
And say, look at this.
It says that mike here
is eight times a lady!
What? What am I even
doing in there?
Wow. Let me take a look at ya,
there, mike.
Ooh, yeah, I see it.
I see it.
Cut it out.
We’ll be right back.
I’m no times a lady.
Say, what are ya doin’ with
your fine self on saturday?
I am not a lady. Not at all.
Not even a little.
Mike, relax.
Even being a hundred times
a lady isn’t a bad thing.
You should know,
ya big woman.
What’s that supposed
to mean, ya giant lady?
Ch--why I oughta...
Oh. Speaking of ladies,
uh, sort of--
uh, whatcha got
for us, pearl?
Oh, hi.
Uh, mike, is it?
Anywho, nothin’ much
goin’ on around here
except the government
has asked me to do
some secret
lsd tests on robots.
Okay, the government’s
not really involved.
They’re just
my secret lsd tests.
Now, brain guy
sent up some stuff
so I can monitor
the results
right on.
Eh-eh-eh-eh mike,
do pearl a little favor
and hook up
the video and co-ax cables
so i˯ can monitor
the robots’ hallucinations.
Uh, okay, pearl.
Looks like we’re set up here.
Now, i’m not gonna tell you
how you’ll be ingesting the lsd
it’s a secret.
Who wants vegetables?
You do! You do!
Hey, brain guy.
Now, to heighten the effect,
bobo and brain guy
have come up with their
own little garage band
to play some of the
psychedelic music
that all the kids
are talking about these days.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you "narcotic casserole."
Now let’s see what’s goin’ on
in those little pea brains of
yours.
Mm. Okay. We’ve got our
vegetables here.
So, uh, let’s switch
it to video feed.
Servo. Servo. Are you--
what a nightmare. Are you okay?
What? Th-- that?
No, mike, that’s what I see
everyday! Heh heh heh.
Let’s check in on crow, here.
How ya doin’?
Mm. Beta-carotene.
Mm. Plenty of fiber. Mm.
Powerful hallucinogens.
Ooh. Okay, uh, let’s switch
to video feed now.
Oh-- oh no-- eeh, ahh--
before, it was a milky-way.
Now-- now it’s a snickers!
Make it stop!
Make it stop, bro!
It’s gonna be okay.
I’m gonna talk ya down.
Snickers! Milky-way!
Argh-- scary! Scary!
Thanks a lot, pearl.
Yeah, pearl,
I hope you’re happy.
I am happy.
Robot mis-identified
candy bar.
Now, your movie today
is a little tab of orange
sunshine called,
"future war."
We have a word for this
kind of film
in the illicit pharmacology
business:
"Crap."
[Laughs]
What?
[Continues laughing]
Crow, you’re
hallucinating a clown.
You mean you’re
not a clown, or--?
We’ve got movie sign!
[Alarm beeping]
Whoa, boy.
Feel better, crow?
My shirt sleeves are
around here, somewhere.
Making a bad movie?
That’s two weeks
in solitary confinement.
[Liquid dripping]
Is that you leaking, crow?
Uh, no.
This place looks like a maze.
We call it a "corn."
Look over there.
Hm?
You make such a big deal
out of feeding the chickens.
Let’s go.
Why’d you make your
hot tub so big?
We found ’em.
Down there.
Let’s get ’em.
I’m right behind you.
So you’ll cushion
my fall.
Uh, could I be in
your movie too?
It’s a clown loft.
People just keep
comin’ out of it.
[Gulp]
Welcome to pipe world.
All we do are pipes,
and we do them well.
Three lesbians
on a dangerous mission.
[Gulp]
[Scream]
Hold on, man. I got ya.
Sorry. My calf just rolled
up like a window shade.
Very deep.
Oh. They set
a gullible moron trap.
Mom just sent us
to the basement
for more pickles.
I didn’t know
it would be this hard.
Our pretending there’s a hole
there is going really well.
Hey, it’s
jean-claude van damme.
Eh, he’s more like
jean-claude gosh darn.
Am I ving rhames?
I can’t remember.
Hmm.
Four days ago,
a fire fell from the sky.
And it brought a man who would
change my life forever.
Deepak chopra.
But also came a pack
of dinosaur-like creatures.
For cute.
In various ages,
shapes, sizes,
and its masters.
Hmm? What?
For all the questions
I had about the heavens,
all it brought
was hell on earth.
All the bras were
hell on earth?
I don’t know
if that’s what--
hey, listen.
Is that a heartbeat?
Oh, no, i’m sorry.
That’s a love beat.
Yeah.
I hear we got flashlights
and a dark space.
Let’s make a movie!
[Scoffs]
So, what are you guys doin’
after whatever we’re doin’ here?
You wanna go
to applebee’s, or...
Remember.
We don’t have hall passes,
so be careful.
[Laughs]
Rock ’em sock ’em dinosaurs.
Mine’s not cooked through.
Go go go go go go go go!
[Scream]
She’s gargling
with fright.
Hurry!
String. I see string.
So it wasn’t
a giant meteor.
It was a daisy air rifle
that killed the dinosaurs.
Jerry! No!
He was three days
away from retirement!
Let’s go!
You know, half this movie has
been people’s butts on ladders.
[Screams]
Dino, no!
In association with bob tet
offensive productions.
Ah, they’re promising
entertainment,
but i’m not
that optimistic.
Wait. Another
movie’s started.
Dust buster galactica.
Maybe this is an anthology
of short, plotless movies.
Could be.
So?
[Laughs]
Traveling at a moderate
15 miles per hour,
we made our way,
safely, through space.
Oh, z’no!
A place!
Here to sing his
top-ten country hit.
[Door creaks]
Hey. William conrad’s
cat-scan machine.
Whew.
Formerly of kazja goo goo.
I think.
Well,
they sent the ship up,
but they forgot
to put in astronauts.
NAMES WITHOUT Zs IN THEM?
What the hell?
The spaceship is handicap
accessible. That’s nice.
Patrick, wait.
Come back and be in the movie.
Oh, now.
[Drill whirring]
I am a camera.
Ah! There’s a "z."
We’re back on track now.
[Drill continues]
Um, we’re still
building the set.
Keep the credits going.
My bra strap broke.
Oh, he’s the french
country singer.
Yeah he’s usually teamed
with guillaume tubbs.
[Drill whirring]
Hey! He’s coming
into the theater, mike.
It would be a lot
more special
if we knew who
the hell he was.
Yeah, arlan h. Boll!
Okay, okay.
I had a bottle
of dom magwilli once.
It was overrated.
Romeo was restless,
he was ready to production
design.
Gesundheit.
Hmm. Creature effects.
Hopefully this
doesn’t mean alf.
It’s the face of a snow monkey
heading at us.
[Imitates monkey]
I’m gonna ignore
this credit.
Just gonna look away
till it’s gone.
Still there.
Okay.
Two first names from van halen.
Coincidence?
Yes.
Yeah.
Save the neutrogena bar!
[Imitates engine]
This movie is crediting
the entire united states,
person by person.
Ew!
Awkward initials.
[Scoffs]
[Humming]
Not a very good tent.
See?
This is what happens when
you de-regulate credits.
Tall, man.
Yeah.
After making a couple
of rest stops along the way.
And...
Withdrawals
from earth’s banks.
Gerbils, well,
they pretty much remained
gerbils.
Questions?
Please refer to the addendum.
And now,
"ooh, heaven is a place on
earth," the movie.
Future wax!
Uh, war.
Oh, yeah.
[Laughs] Sorry.
Aw. Cute little credits.
Don’t be shy.
Come on up here.
Come on up.
[Kisses]
I’m having a secret storm
right now, mike.
Don’t tell anyone.
Okay.
Three mile island
all-inclusive resort.
Write ’em.
Ugh. It’s tough swimming
in this part of the ocean.
A giant chicken!
Bawk.
Uh, he’s gonna
need a big bag
to pick up after
his dinosaur.
I’m tellin’.
You got a pet on the beach.
Wow. They lit this
with a kfc heat lamp.
Chuck wepner’s
point of view.
[Scoffs]
Later, in houston,
or portland,
or some crappy hole
of a town, I don’t know.
Hey, it’s mike!
Oh, no.
Santa claus
hits the skids.
Kind of an ineffective
beer commercial.
Gimme back my beer!
Aah!
[Growling]
[Yelling]
Well, I better
get back to the office.
[Laughs]
I warn you,
my meat is very stringy.
[Yelling]
This has gotta be kinda
the last danger you think of
when you’re
living in a dumpster.
Yup.
[Growling]
He’s a cute-a-saurus.
He’s being attacked
by a schnauzer
in a dinosaur costume.
Oh.
Wow.
Well, that was easy.
Maybe it was butterflies
that wiped out
the dinosaurs.
Tap dogs.
Ooh!
No wonder fossils
are so rare.
I’ll disguise myself
as a box.
Must look corrugated
and square.
Thank you!
Wow.
Being a scab for ups is hard.
Alan jackson
in a very special cameo.
[Laughs]
It’s a weird,
threatening clown.
Hey,
they got good stuff
here at the police auction.
Van-damme it.
[Lens focusing]
Brain guy looked like this
in high school.
[Laughs]
Damn binocular trick.
Aah!
Geez, i’m sorry
I killed your dinosaur.
I didn’t know
he was a pet.
Boxes of air,
shipped anywhere in the world,
overnight.
Boing! Boing!
He’s got clown white
all over his fists now.
Wow,
maybe they ship fully-inflated
balloons overseas.
World’s grouchiest mime.
He’s "boxed" in!
Yeah,
well, i’m "card-bored."
[Laughter]
Shut up, you two.
Be honest.
Am I wearing too much eyeliner?
So he sees considerably worse
than humans.
I like the
randy johnson-model cyborg.
The fed-ex / dhl wars continued
well into the next century.
Ugh.
Don’t come in yet! Ugh!
The truth about radio...
Aah!
Cardboard boxes
aren’t working.
Try throwing
a piece of paper
or a cottonball.
Aah!
Ah. This is hard
to watch because
I care about them both
so much.
I care about the boxes.
Why should innocent freight
have to suffer?
He looks better
without makeup.
Yeah, he’s so pretty.
He really doesn’t need it.
Battle of the guys
who peaked in high school.
Aah!
[Laughter]
[Guttural noises]
Ugh. I got
point of view vertigo here.
My trained weiner
will finish you off!
Aah!
Baah!
Merengue!
♪ Doo doo doo ♪
I’ll just wait ’til
you’re done twirling.
Augh!
[Laughs]
Packers!
So these guys
are kung-fu fighting.
[Laughter]
[Objects clattering]
My bell collection!
Aah! Uh-- ah?
[Growling]
[Grunts]
The largest attempt ever
to lock in freshness.
This part was filmed
through soup.
Hmm.
Kim wilde could
do a video here.
I’m all moved in, but i’m still
living out of boxes.
He’s using sense memory.
An actor prepares...
To suck.
He studied under
lee strasberg’s car.
He’s read uta hagen’s
"respect for acting...
Like an imbecile."
You know, he should probably
throw an empty box
just to keep
from gettin’ rusty.
[Growling]
I’m doing the
making-out-with-myself gag
and no one’s here
to enjoy it.
Geez,
where’d I pack the can opener?
I continue
to remain cold.
Oh, the warehouse covered
everything in vinyl
so no one sits
on their good boxes.
[Growling]
Mm. Do I have something
in my teeth? Mm.
All right. There should be
a delay-of-movie penalty
right about now.
[Whistle]
Fifteen yards.
[Growling]
Kool-aid vision.
Nothing, nothing.
I don’t hear ya,
dinosaur.
La la la la la.
Don’t year ya.
This dinosaur used to rule
hollywood.
Now spielberg won’t
return his calls.
Mm. Sad.
Ch-ya!
Yow!
That hurts!
[Laughs]
Killed by a pencil!
Lay that ham up there.
There we go.
There’s the new legs,
but I don’t think
they’re gonna be very
functional.
That’s okay.
Thanks, mike.
Hello, folks!
You may be wondering
why i’m not kickboxing right
now.
I apologize.
You have every right to expect
constant kickboxing!
But the truth is,
until recently I had no legs.
However! I just remedied that
by actually making myself some!
Haha!
So get ready for some hot
kickboxing action!
The first poor shmoe comes along
is gonna get a taste of my
ashley judd-like
kickboxing wrath.
♪ You shook me
all night long ♪
Ah, a challenger.
Hi, tom.
Ha! You dare to oppose me,
strange top-heavy purple one?
What?
Prepare to be kickboxed
by my new legs!
I don’t wanna fight,
tom.
I like you.
You will fight,
coward!
[Grunting]
Gosh dang it!
Come on, legs!
They’re pretty new legs,
tom.
Fawning flattery
will not help you.
[Grunt]
Dumb, stupidy, stinky legs.
Oh! Aah! Wow!
Oh, boy!
Oh, geez!
Just a temporary setback.
Do you need help,
tom?
No! No.
[Grunts]
Phew!
There.
Now stop your
pathetic delaying tactics.
I insist you fight me,
weakling!
Well,
if you want.
Okay, tom.
Oh. Oh, boy!
Hi-ya!
Ow!
[Crashing]
Sorry.
I thought you didn’t
have legs either!
Just made it today.
Neat, huh?
We’ll be right back.
I should make
another one.
Oh.
[Gasps]
Wow.
Sister vehicular homicide.
Oh, great.
Third time this week.
I’ll just leave
a note on him.
Yeah, he’s alive.
Somebody help me!
Please!
Help me,
sister roscoe.
Fred.
Oh, fred.
I’m all
flibbertigibbet.
In the car.
A man.
Her hair weave
doesn’t blend in that well.
There’s an injured man
in the car.
He needs our help.
Hey, oscar!
We need your help outside.
I’ll loan him
some flesh.
Ann?
Long time no see.
She’s wearing
a maternity habit.
Your van
is under arrest
for not having "scene"
painted on the side.
The van must be having
emissions problems.
It’s blackened
the lower atmosphere.
Hey, what do we’ve got?
Homeless guy with his
throat ripped out.
By what?
Who cares?
Figure mountain lion, grizzlies
come out of the hills
in search of food.
Found this
poor bastard instead.
Great.
Just great.
Has anybody called
the humane society?
The zoo?
They’re sending
some people out.
Captain!
He dropped
something here.
I found part of a burger.
I wanna know if I can eat it?
It’s not that dirty.
Split it with ya.
We found this.
What the hell made that?
That’s your shadow,
boss.
[Birds chirping]
Jesus.
I think I should
be wearing a tie.
Ow!
Oh, my gout!
I mean,
don’t give me a hard time,
okay?
I think you
broke a bone.
I mean,
what is this bull?
no special favors.
Okay,
anything you say.
[...]
And watch that language.
Okay, okay.
Hey, so now you don’t like
my cooking, sister?
Oh, no.
I’m just not hungry.
Thanks for cookin’.
Hey, I have some
nice chocolate cake,
some mocha almond
ice cream.
Hey i’ll have some.
No, thanks.
I think i’ll pass.
Is this a halfway house
for huge guys?
[Laughter]
This is worse
than I thought.
There’s no butter
in my coffee.
You’re at home now,
annie.
So what’s goin’ on?
Whoa!
That’s what’s goin’ on!
Okay, let’s see.
I’ll take his wallet,
and his echinacea,
ooh,
and his goat cheese.
Should I?
YES I’LL TAKE HIS
’70s WATCH.
You know maybe i’m--
maybe i’m not
meant for this.
Maybe i’m meant
for something else.
Maybe.
Sister superior says
that i’m having
a crisis of faith.
[Imitates belch]
Maybe.
Well, what do you think?
I think I like
the haagen dazs better.
Maybe.
Come on.
I’m looking for some
counseling here, fred.
Hey, I cut meat,
ya know?
Personally, I think you’re
getting a little stupid
about that kid that
bought the farm.
Hmm?
Remember jimmy ho?
Remember lena melcher?
I heard about terry.
Mink stole.
Sorry.
How’s our guest?
Unconscious.
Look what I found.
Calista flockhart’s
belt.
Maybe he’s into some kinda
bondage thing.
Smart guy.
I patched up what I could
without x-rays.
I’ll know more tomorrow.
Why don’t you have
a seat, nurse?
Yeah, come on.
Sit down.
Nah, no time.
I gotta get back
to the clinic.
Terrible habit,
girl.
Hey, not on the floor.
It’s good to have you back,
ann.
Thanks.
I’ll stop by after my shift,
okay?
Bye.
Hey, you want somethin’,
max?
Uncle fred says
you don’t have a husband.
you’re gonna shave your head
and turn into
a penguin.
A penguin.
Can I watch?
It was a metaphor.
He says you don’t know
what you’re doing.
Max. It’s time
to go to bed now.
Go brush your teeth.
Go on.
Say goodnight.
Night,
mom and dad.
You’re right,
you know.
Aw, come on, annie.
I was just talkin’.
Mm, two days ago
I was so sure.
And what?
Today you don’t know nothin’?
It’s hard being
a nun with a family.
Look. When we met,
you were hiding from a pimp.
You just did a month
in the joint.
You were suicidal
and addicted.
And ya threw
it all away.
Keeping you in here
was hard.
When lena was killed
by some guy
wired up on the drugs
he bought from me.
Aw, come off it,
annie.
It’s like I pulled
the trigger.
But you didn’t.
He did.
You came here.
Got clean.
You helped other girls
off the junk
and off the street.
Hmph.
That means something,
annie.
It means great service
and low, low prices.
[Sigh]
I was a great hooker.
I’m gonna go up north
and visit an aunt.
She lives
on an "aunt" farm.
[Laughter]
Take care of that guy.
Listen, kid.
Everything’s gonna
work out just fine.
You’ll see.
Ah.
What if god was one of us?
I hope so.
[Crickets]
Promise margarine.
A new kind of spread.
Guess he’s awake.
Yup.
How’s he doing?
Okay.
I tried to talk to him.
English. Spanish.
He doesn’t talk,
but I think he understands.
I left him
in the day-care room.
Hmm.
Let’s go have a look.
They must go through
a lot of zubaz in this house.
Mm-hmm.
And maybe he can tell us
what this thing is for.
Where’re you goin’?
I’m gonna
go to my room and pack.
I wanna be on the road
by 12:00.
Oh, no.
Aren’t you gonna stay
and help us with this guy?
He’s yours.
Yeah, sister, come on.
You’re good at this
kind of thing.
They don’t get
the all-kickboxing station.
Sorry, I ate your
breakfast on the way in.
[Static]
It’s hard to sample
off the radio.
Mm.
[Imitates flatulence]
Oh, sorry.
That’s not very appetizing,
is it?
[Laughs]
I just thought of a great joke
from nunsense.
Good thing we switched
places there.
Hi there, i’m fred.
That’s romero and that’s
sister ann.
I assume you’ve met your
corn with pimentos.
Hey, man,
what’s your story?
A macy’s balloon.
Oh, it’s you. Hi.
You understand english?
Ah. He’s gonna
fit right in.
♪ All his pants
are low-riders ♪
♪ doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo ♪
Where’s that light station
that everyone can listen to
at home, in the car,
or at the office?
Uh, who’s up for a snack?
Two huge dinosaurs.
Uh--oh, it’s those guys.
Leave me alone with him.
This guy might be a psycho.
And,
um what do you think?
He’s gonna open up
with you in there?
Well, why not?
I’m a likable guy.
The sad thing is they’re
all former prostitutes.
Gimme the collar.
You just say the word.
I’ll be right outside
the door.
It was fun to be in here
for a while,
but now let’s
go in there again.
[Static continues]
Must be minneapolis.
He can’t find a good station.
German? Dutch? Huh?
Hmm?
Hey, you like the pictures
in the magazines?
What other random things
can I say?
Lamp?
Elephants in the street?
[Sighs]
Is this yours?
I’m gonna wear it
to the rave tonight.
Hang your crappy art
high on the wall.
This is a con.
You can hear us,
and I think you
understand us.
Us being me and the lamp.
You wanna give
us a break?
[Radio music]
Mm. That bass.
Somewhere seinfeld
must be starting.
Guess not.
Well, enjoy.
I don’t think
I will enjoy,
if it’s all right with you.
Great warren moon
impression.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
[Breathing heavily]
Well.
Thank you
for not killing me.
They should make
a hallmark card for that.
Mm. Hmm.
Hey, you’re the same size
as my alsatian.
Oh. Oh.
There’s...
There’s something wrong with
your throat.
Yeah.
You can understand us,
but you can’t talk, right?
Is that it? Is that it?
No, just chokin’ ya.
When I nod my head like this,
I mean "yes."
Is that it? Yes?
And when I shake my head no,
I mean "no."
Right? Yes.
Yes.
We’re all out of steak.
Where are you from?
Hey, maybe you can write.
Okay. Um...
A, b, c.
It’s not even "ass,"
servo.
Go on.
[Pronounces alphabet
phonetically]
Not a clue.
He’s got lady weightlifter
cleavage.
Hey, the map.
Let’s see...
Here?
[Grunts]
Are you from here?
Canary islands? Morocco?
New jersey? Hong kong?
Sauk rapids? What?
Here?
[Moans]
Eh... oh, you’re from eh.
[Grunts]
I live in your air vent.
I’m sorry I can’t
understand.
Oh. Oh. Up here?
[Moans]
You thick woman. Man!
What happened?
We were batter-dipping.
Hi. My name’s max.
Hi. I’m your toy.
Pleased to meet you.
Hi. My name’s max.
Hmm?
[Grunting]
Where are you going?
I’m gonna go visit
an aunt I have up north.
I just came
to say goodbye.
[Grunts]
So goodbye.
Hey, don’t worry.
They’re gonna take good care--
hey.
Well, maybe now you can
tell me where you come from.
- You...
- [Grunting]
Here...
I...come...
I’m sorry
I don’t understand.
I wasn’t done.
I’m sorry.
The son of moe howard.
I’ll hit you so hard
with this,
you’ll go flying
that way, and--
yeah.
Max, did you show him
any space videos?
Yeah.
Hey, you know your
sprinkler was on?
Are all nuns so stupid?
[Screams]
Damn bumpus’s dinosaurs.
Save the meat loaf.
Yeah, this happens
a couple times a day.
No! They’re my friends!
Run. Must run.
Amway.
Whaa.
Hey, it’s a full aspirin
out tonight.
Ugh. Glad the dinosaur
got the kid.
Really distracted him.
God.
Thank you.
[Grunts]
I think we’ve
outrun them.
You are a penguin?
No, i’m a puffin.
No. I’m a sister.
Not a penguin.
You know,
one of the sledge girls.
You know...
How is it you know
english today
when you didn’t
know english yesterday?
Uh, bad screenwriting,
really.
It was hard for me
to understand him.
For all the problems
I had,
maybe I just didn’t want
to be a part of his.
He explained to me how
quickly he could learn,
how his vocal cords needed
to adjust to speak our tongue,
and how he had heard
our words before.
Go ahead.
His eyes were so honest,
but still there was a part
of him that I didn’t trust.
And who are you?
A tool.
I’m a boxwrench.
And you come from--?
Uh, just let me check the wind
and i’ll tell ya.
Never mind.
[Bells clanging]
Trains bringing in food
for the roommates.
Well, I suppose one of us
has to play harmonica.
Want a little
convent-issued pot here?
Here.
Will you chew it
and regurgitate it for me?
Mm.
[Laughs]
Whoa.
I needed that jerky.
You’re human.
And you’re
putting up with me.
I am...Tool.
Call me "snap-on."
And you’re from up there.
The pagam.
The first were harvested
from this world,
like, trackers long ago.
I preferred his grunting.
We are used to build
because...
We have these.
Hamburglar finger puppets.
The master
do not have these.
They can make
their own thumbs,
but they just
don’t want to?
They want
us to do the work.
Yeah, I knew
a few pimps in my time.
Pimps?
Did you know rooster?
You wouldn’t understand.
Like the bible says,
my thoughts
are not your thoughts.
Neither are your ways
my ways,
says the lord.
Jack lord.
This is a con.
No, no, no, no.
No. No trick. No lie.
How does an alien-bred human
know quotes from the bible?
In the world where
I am from,
in the place where
the tools are kept
are...
Unsketched with words.
A phrase
told in darkness.
I have heard
your language before.
Well, um, explain this
so I can understand it.
Why are we on this train?
This place
was the most
important story.
Our dream.
Our heaven.
And now,
our gang.
I’m free.
- [Voice over]
He was so honest.
- What?
I explained to him,
about the heavens.
I was studying
to become a nun.
Mm-hmm.
But now i’m having
second thoughts.
I’m mary.
This is my story.
When I was younger,
I ran away and
I have a past that
i’m not proud of.
That’s why I kept
a scrapbook.
[Laughs]
I found the church
and they helped me.
But just recently
a friend of mine, um,
died of a drug overdose.
Pepcid ac.
I blame myself
for her death.
I don’t know.
I feel somehow responsible.
I guess that’s why I blame
myself for the death.
Yeah, I made her swallow
a pound of coke.
She was yelling,
"please stop,"
but still.
[Bells ringing]
The only thing
that keeps me going
is my all-bells cd.
Hey, you know what, guys?
What?
We have been remiss.
I know what
you’re thinking.
Yeah,
you know we have never,
like in the movie,
thanked pearl
for not killing us.
Not once.
Well, let’s do it.
Right now.
Yeah.
Hello, pearl?
[Man over intercom]
Satellite killer launch--
six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
Yeah? What?
Well, uh, pearl,
I don’t know
how else to say this.
Uh, thank you
for not killing us.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Huh?
Well, that’s okay.
Ah--
I would never...
Kill...
Brain guy, get over here.
Hello.
Well, you know,
things get pretty tense
between us.
What with one thing
or another, I mean,
you could easily
have killed us.
And you didn’t do that.
So--so thanks.
Really, that’s okay.
Ah--
I guess I just...
Take it for granted
that I would never...
How do you turn
the rocket?
Well, first you say
you want to kill them,
then you say you don’t
want to kill them.
I mean,
what am I supposed to do?
Well, I can’t
kill them now.
Really, don’t think
a second thing about it.
"It would be so fun to kill
mike and the bots today."
[Grunts]
Um, anything else
you guys wanna add?
I don’t think so.
Just thanks.
For not killing us.
Yeah.
Yeah. That’s okay.
Don’t worry about it.
But, but, but,
aren’t you killing them now?
Shh.
They’re thanking you
for not killing them,
but you’re killing them--
ugh. Oh.
[Grunts]
There. Ready.
Well, I guess
that’s about it.
Just thanks for not ki--
[shouts]
Hey.
Hey, you tried
to kill us.
What the--?
No!
I didn’t. No.
Never.
Yes, you did.
Ugh.
[Scoffs]
Well,
I just think this changes
everything.
I suppose there’s other times
you’ve tried to kill us too.
Oh,
now we have movie sign.
Can I even trust that?
I don’t know.
Sister ann?
Are you all right?
I can’t believe it.
Wow.
Ever since yesterday
at the burial
i’ve been asking myself...
How much
do undertakers make?
What I missed.
You didn’t miss anything,
my dear.
It wasn’t your fault.
How come I wasn’t taken?
Because you weren’t.
And that’s that.
So shut your trap.
I don’t know
if i’m going to take
my final vows next week.
I have a nail appointment.
Because of terry jo?
That’s what this is--?
You know what I was
before I came here.
Sister william
looks concerned.
Well, you had a record.
So did mary magdalene.
I was a whore
doing tricks in back alleys.
I sold drugs.
Sister ann, that was then.
This is then too.
It’s weird.
I’m very proud of you now.
You’re bringing in
a lot of cash
to the convent.
I’m not.
Well, then.
We have a problem here,
don’t we?
She was smart, sister.
Good. Tough.
She was built "ford tough."
Sister.
I should have been there
for her when she needed me.
Sister ann.
Why don’t you take
the weekend?
Go out to the track
or something.
Visit your friends
and family.
Perfection is not
one of the requirements.
Faith is.
Sister.
Do you believe in signs?
I believe in
"yield from right."
I guess I do.
Really? I--i don’t know
what to say.
I thought you were gonna
say no.
Keep your eyes open.
Can’t trust these nuns.
God always answers prayers.
But only from catholics.
We’ll take a brief break
from my flashback now.
What about the tracker?
What happens now?
The tracker will rest.
Then go back.
What was I talking about?
To where it first found us.
Is he talking about
a "warwolf?"
I don’t believe this.
This is a city.
Twelve-million puddy-tats.
Are you going back?
Yes.
But the tracker
has your scent now.
Tough.
He’ll have to deal with it.
If I go with you,
it will find me.
Well then you better
get back on the train.
Say, by the way,
what is "kiss?"
I do not understand.
This is something
I have to do.
I’d like to give you
some big words of wisdom,
but I just don’t have any.
My mind’s blank.
You do what you have to do.
Goodbye.
We don’t have a permit
to shoot on the curb.
Am I a wild and crazy guy?
What are you doing?
Doing what I believe to.
Is that okay at you?
And what’s that?
I’m going with you.
Look.
Let’s get this straight.
I work alone.
I nun outta my home.
Alone.
By myself.
I want to be alone.
Better is a neighbor
that is near
than a brother far off.
Uh, that’s from one of them
"chicken soup" books.
I don’t wanna
talk about this.
Could you button my shirt?
I’m gonna call sister gary
and see if she can cover
my shift.
The number you have reached
is not in service.
Oh, vatican.
Pay your phone bill.
Heaven’s a mess,
isn’t it?
I don’t know.
I like it.
"The alien and the nun."
This fall on cbs.
How many people
got murdered today? Huh?
Or raped? Beaten?
Oh. Missing!
You’re upset.
Yeah, i’m upset.
Didn’t my acting
convey that?
But you want
to help your friends.
And that’s different.
I know them.
You don’t know me.
You helped me.
Greater love
has no man than this...
Than a man lay down
his life...
Heard it.
For his friend.
Ugh.
I gotta get outta here.
Should we be worried
about our friends?
That is what I want to be.
What?
A man.
You are a man.
No.
I mean, greater love.
That kind of man.
You better be careful
what you wish for.
Sister mary despair.
[Laughs]
Ah, life is good.
I live in maui
and I got a monster mag.
[Laughs]
[Growls]
♪ Wastin’ away again
in margaritaville ♪
Ew.
He has the live,
supple figure
of james doohan.
[Growling]
A man was snapped at by
a forced-perspective puppet
today.
We’re going
on the assumption
that some animal
out of the hills
has gone on a rampage.
The body found here
at third street
makes four deaths
in six hours.
This creature knows
where it’s going.
I want cars posted
all along this route.
Make ’em all tercels.
Stay in close radio contact
at all times.
Let’s go.
Is god out there?
He is out there, man!
God of gods.
King of kings.
You don’t even know
what you’re saying, do you?
[Gibberish]
You don’t.
What’s out there?
Is heaven out there?
Earth is heaven.
Thanks to olestra.
And the supreme being
is what?
Well,
it’s not earl holliman.
Handlers. Masters.
No, no, no, no. Not them.
Greater than them.
What is your word
for "boring?"
[Laughs]
The movie’s dragging,
then they show us soccer.
Good.
Soccer’s my game.
I’ve no arms, ya see.
Aah!
[Phone ringing]
"Puffy hat police."
Western division.
Officer fry speaking.
How may I help you?
Hello.
This is mailboxes etc.
People really need our boxes.
Be calm, sir.
Help us. Please.
[Laughs]
Man. Why’d we take
the train to sacramento?
I’m supposed to get you folks
back in the movie.
10-4 unit 41-k.
905-v in progress.
Fifth street warehouse.
Code three.
It’s the world’s
most put-upon nun.
This is boris becker
reporting live.
This is wcng reporter...
[Laughter]
Reporting to you live
from the fifth street
warehouse
where there has been
a reported animal attack.
[Laughter]
Ted nugent helps out.
More updates as they occur.
Thanks for playing reporter
and camera guy with me.
I think the cardboard camera’s
working good.
[Laughter]
Captain,
there are employees
still in the plant
at the back of a store room.
He’s reporting
over a baby monitor.
Joey,
lead in the tactical team.
You take the point.
Ugh. Now, I have unbridled
enthusiasm for boxes, mike,
you know that.
But even I think
they’ve overdone
the box theme
in this movie.
Okay, boxes. If you have any
inserts throw ’em out now.
I really do like boxes.
Yeah.
Just call me
"bruce box-liker."
[Laughs]
Oh.
Please?
I don’t think so.
Okay.
Ugh. Mandy patinkin’s gonna
do a concert back there.
Hey, joey.
Captain wants to know if you’ve
spotted that bear yet.
No--no, sir.
Try a pick-a-nick basket,
boo boo.
Hmm?
Where’s the rest
of my swat team?
Am I just a swat guy?
I just found the blood stains.
This looks fresh.
And i’ve tried
scrubbing them out.
You sure it’s not ketchup?
No, sir. It’s real.
Focus on, uh, polaris.
And arctic cat.
What happened?
You two. Follow me.
They were transferred
to a costa-gavras film.
All patrols.
Northeast corner.
Your lights are on.
Uh, anybody got
a bloody glove we could plant?
Sweet jesus.
Leo.
Reminds me of the time
chief gates chunked all over
headquarters.
Ugh.
Sometimes tools will run.
When the trackers catch them,
it’s like this.
So, uh, wally,
you need a doctor or...?
[Gunshots]
The dinosaur is skeet shooting
off the port bow.
[Growling]
Hey, it’s coming back.
The movie that
pushes over boxes.
Don’t shoot.
Floyd’s behind ’em.
Might hit each other.
I’ve got floyd.
Can you kill him with that?
Yeah. Here. Cut here.
It’s the softest place.
Ooh.
How long?
Just a moment.
Don’t miss.
This is how dinosaurs
see plaid.
This is a case where parents
should have crushed
a child’s dream
of becoming a filmmaker.
Mm. Right.
Aah!
So when you edit it,
it’ll look like I stabbed him,
right?
I was coming to warn you.
An asteroid...
Ugh...
Swat guy who’s dead
must be feelin’ pretty dumb
right now.
[Beeping]
That’s mine. I got it.
Get down!
Oh. I had a woodchuck
do this to me once.
[Laughs]
Well.
Captain polaris.
[Laughter]
Captain polaris?
Are you there?
We got the bastard, sergeant.
We’ve got a situation here.
What do you mean
you got a situation?
I mean we’ve got more monster
sightings in the city.
More?
How could there be more?
They come in packs.
Or cartons.
They’re after me.
They will continue
to hurt people
until they find me.
Bring me to them.
Otis. Smitty.
Place this man under arrest.
Hey. He just saved you and
everybody in the building
from that thing.
That’s right.
He’s not a criminal.
He won’t run away
this time.
Now, if you’ll excuse us,
sister ann,
your friend’s got
some questions to answer.
Hey.
How did you know who I was?
Fred burroughs told us how
he got you to give him a ride,
but don’t worry.
You’re free to go.
Fred burroughs.
Somebody look in your rolodex
for a fred burroughs.
Who’s fred burroughs?
Fred burroughs! Help me!
A skinny, belgian idiot
was arraigned on charges
early today.
Well, I am belgian.
[Static]
Hey, the l.a. police
got themselves a boombox.
And a copier.
Whoo.
[Laughs]
...has caused a number
of wild animals to escape
from the zoo.
They are extremely
dangerous.
[Imitates monkey]
Just wait until fred burroughs
gets here, man.
[Grunts]
Ugh. Haven’t had hardee’s
in over an hour.
They don’t care about us,
annie.
They just cut us loose.
In fact,
everybody cut footloose.
Is terry jo’s brother
still running with
the 12th street gang?
Yeah.
Can you set up
a meeting with me?
What for?
You’re such a nun.
So he can shoot me.
[Laughs]
We’re sharing
a vague moment.
[Laughs]
Ladies and gentlemen,
fred burroughs.
[Laughter]
We’re number one.
Based on a play by
terrence mcnally.
Hmm?
Maybe he is
tom of finland.
Could be.
Hey, little pal.
Where’d my thumb go?
Cha.
He’s beating up
his memories.
Cha.
He’s warming up to sing
the big country song.
Cha.
Uh, pretty soon
he’s gonna be flashing back
to the beginning
of the flashback.
Cha!
That pretty much
brings us up to speed.
Thank you, soloflex.
Well, i’m all "cha’d" out.
I wonder if I get body waxing
privileges in here.
The things my stereo
came packed in fly
through space.
A mark vii production.
So?
Oh good. Another large guy.
The movie was needing one.
[Laughs]
Well, their stair-climbing
lessons seem to be going well.
♪ Beat it
beat it ♪
You got something
to say to me?
I’m sorry I took
your parking space.
Sorry about terry jo.
He was a good python.
Anything else?
I’m sorry.
She had deep thoughts,
you know?
Is he a sister hazel,
mike?
I need your help.
For what?
I need to borrow your tuke.
Monsters in the ’hood.
Meanwhile, in the life
of a basement-dwelling
computer nerd...
But never mind that.
Let’s go here.
These are things.
They exist.
Wow.
So.
Dr. Tanaka.
What’s your honest opinion?
What’s there not to believe?
A race of transplanted humans
bred on another planet...
One of them escapes,
returns to his
ancestral world,
and these dinosaurs and their
masters are here to bring him
back.
Personally I think he’s nuts.
Detective alan thicke.
I’ve seen these dinosaurs,
doctor.
They’re real.
Maybe his story
is real too.
Captain...
Federal agents.
We’re taking over this case
as of right now.
But my puffy hair.
Under who’s authority?
National security, captain.
You’re hereby relieved
of this case
and ordered
to leave the room now.
I’m taking this
to the commissioner!
Why, if this door wasn’t
just a flat panel i’d...
I don’t believe this.
Can you explain this?
They’re photographs.
I said,
can you explain this?
They’re trackers.
When the tracker was killed,
what happened to his body?
Self-destruct.
So they leave no trace.
Trice?
Trice.
Like this?
Dee snyder’s dance belt.
You look so human.
I’m a man.
In my particular
relationship.
So you say.
Sorry. This nipple ring’s
hard to remove.
Well?
It appears to be a transmitter
of some kind.
I’m taking it to the lab.
Can you all leave the room,
please?
Say, you wanna get my polyp
while you’re at it?
I apologize for this
humiliation. It’s my job.
I have a job too.
I’m a tool.
My life is my job.
Mine too.
Oh, okay. You both have
interesting jobs.
Don’t fight about it.
Barbara, here.
Take a look at this.
And send the results
to my office, please.
Look, they draped stuff
in front of the editing machine.
Payless shoes
can be uncomfortable.
Dr. Pam tillis.
Oh,
his exterior patellas hurt.
Sorry.
Thought I saw a deer
in there.
[Gasps]
Noogie!
Easy spirit lab shoes.
Won’t anyone give me five?
Danger restroom area?
Uh, yeah.
A coworker has
irritable bowel syndrome.
Ah.
I got caught
in the towel machine.
[Laughs]
Freddie mercury
after a good beating.
[Screams]
[Laser blasts]
Ah. Vapor action.
Hmm.
Do I put this
on my time card?
She did him the favor
of pre-stuffing herself
in the crawl space.
[Yells]
[Gasps]
Future doctor
of chiropractic.
[Machine whirring]
What’s that noise?
His timing belt
must be loose.
[Laughs]
Willis.
What you talking ’bout?
Dexter.
We’re taking him to the...
I’m going back to being
the apostle, boss.
Okay, paperwork. Talk.
[Explosion]
What is it?
You know, don’t ya?
[Moans]
It’s a giant-faced
bruno kirby.
Somebody shot the editor.
[Laughs]
Shot in the lounge
of a college dormitory.
On any given night.
Mm.
Aah!
Aah! Ricky.
Woops. Banana peel.
[Screams]
The l.a.p.d. gun closet.
Can I borrow your shirt?
Aah!
Let’s do some crimes.
Say "uncle."
Uncle.
That’s right.
Now gimme your lunch money.
Freeze, damn it.
Oh. That was dumb.
This isn’t a real movie.
It’s more of a movie loaf.
Yeah, it’s made from
real movie parts,
chunked and formed.
Mm.
[Nervous laughter]
Anyway,
thanks for listening.
It’s just my little arms
are kind of frustrating.
Here,
let me pick your teeth.
You’ve got a huge piece
of chive stuck in there.
Okay. My theory is that
the director shot
the entire movie
without looking at it.
[Laughs]
That was good.
It’s the big one.
I’m comin’, elizabeth.
Ah, that’s how you
kill an android--
you wipe a length of thin pipe
across his stomach.
[Beeping]
Uh oh.
And like spent lovers,
they lay together.
Can’t count on the police.
Can’t count on anybody.
What do you want us to do?
We can stop these things
together.
Yeah right.
"Together."
"Together" means
we do all the work, right?
No. We’re outta here.
Sit your ass down.
Sister’s right.
Nobody’s gonna
help us but us.
They got the neighborhood
by the balls.
Don’t scare us.
Don’t see ya on the streets,
either.
That’s enough.
Let ’em go.
They don’t have to help us
if they don’t want to.
You sayin’ we’re afraid?
No.
But there’s gonna be a fight.
And it’s gonna be bad,
and it’s gonna be bloody.
So where do we find
these things?
Ugh. Sorry i’m late.
My sleeves fell off.
Always near water.
Water.
That could be a lot
of places.
Then we do it the hard way,
and we look.
Water obviously cut this fence
and broke through.
Meanwhile on the african queen,
bogart and hepburn
pick leeches off each other.
Water.
Uh, the crips like to go down
to the reflecting pool
for their gang retreats.
Yo.
Let’s collect wildflowers.
Hey,
an outer vomitorium.
Hmm.
Thought that was a baby ruth.
Wait.
Is that a clark bar?
Come here.
Fresh tracks.
Oh no.
They’re a day old.
They’ve been marked down.
Very deep.
[Growling]
Run!
Who are they?
Get on a truck!
[Growling]
♪ I’m your puppet ♪
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go.
Drive the car!
Go!
The hell you doing
in my truck?
Taxi!
Drive!
Surge!
Look, how much more
can I drive?
There’s no inherent quantity
of driving
that I can increase.
If you want me to faster
then you need to tell me that.
[Laughs]
The character of bob
the friendly security guard
implied here.
God.
We’re gonna be massacred.
We’re gonna
have to take a stand tonight.
You will attack the trackers?
You got something better?
Listen.
They’re after me.
I will give myself to them.
Good. Meeting adjourned.
But they are after him.
Can these things die?
The utne reader staff.
Yeah.
Come on, man.
You’re talking
heavy artillery.
We can’t get
anything like that.
Mm. Good coffee.
Yes we can.
Is this yours?
No. I didn’t...
Aah!
Hello.
I’m droppy
the water droplet.
Here to talk to you
about water.
Nature’s liquid.
Okay. Why?
Well,
in today’s motion picture
much was made
of the propensity of dinosaurs
to gather near water.
I remember one line.
And yet, sadly water
was not featured.
Uh, that’s true.
And so i’ve been hired
by the water council
to dispel some of the myths
being propagated
probably by jealous solids
and semi-solids
about this tremendously
versatile fluid.
Oh.
Well.
Now where the hell
did he go?
[Campy music]
Hello. I’m droppy
the water droplet.
Yes you are.
Did you know that
there are literally
tens of thousands
of uses for water?
Here are
just a few thousand.
Moisten your hair with me
and apply
a commercial-grade detergent.
Lather, rinse and repeat
for a cleaner-smelling head.
Crow, I think we’re all
familiar with--
send me through your
lower atmosphere
freezing me into multifaceted,
crystalline patterns.
Children enjoy
my easy shapeability.
Store me in huge,
glass-lined tanks,
and allow grains
and yeast to ferment in me.
Then just filter,
age and bottle me
for a treat that
dad’s can’t resist.
Are these in any
kind of order?
Sir, we’ve got a lot
of these to go through
so if you could
please hold your water.
[Laughs]
The water council
fed me that one.
Anyway.
Use me in your
cellular structure
as an affordable
building block of life itself.
Store me frozen on your
inefficient roofs,
allowing portions
of me to melt
and re-freeze on your eaves
in beautiful, conical shapes.
You know what? We’ll tell you
what you missed...
Use me to flush toxins
from your body
and store me in your bladder.
Okay. That’s about enough.
Then--what? What?
[Laughs]
Nice, crow.
The mean streets of burbank.
I’m jumpy the pusher.
Conroy.
♪ Doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo ♪
I need some weapons.
Some real heavy stuff.
I got you a ford pinto.
They’re great weapons.
Oh, oh. Wait. Do you wanna
kill other people?
Hey, annie.
Hello, chadwick.
How’s your catalog of cheap,
women’s apparel?
We go back don’t we?
We go way back.
I’m not here
to talk about that.
Hold it. Okay, okay.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean nothin’.
I come to contribute.
Here.
Here’s some zucchini loaf.
What’s this?
Pound of high-grade white.
Killing dose?
[...] Kill
a whole city block.
And there’s this.
Dollar off
on tide detergent.
Every war needs
some finance, babe.
Who’s that?
None of your business.
Guess you gotta take
the bad with the good, huh?
Goodnight, sister.
I gotta go manage
a denny’s.
Hey. Casablanca.
Would you dopple me into that,
mike?
[Laughs]
Sister suzuki sidekick.
Conroy.
I got the money.
Now can you help?
Sure, annie.
Ah,
pushing’s kinda slow today.
Fine. Get in.
Okay. We’ll open a petsmart here
and a home depot there.
Hmm?
Oh. It’s one of those things
that cops always hit me with.
Okay, and waldenbooks here
and a couple starbucks.
Would you stop messing around
with that flashlight
and help us?
Ch-yeah.
So, in the future they simply
forgot about flashlights.
[Laughs]
These have nothing
to do with each other.
[Laughs]
It’s great they got a french
resistance fighter
to help them.
Uh, this will have to pass
for humor.
Until actual humor
can be found,
please enjoy
this substitute.
Uh-huh. Great.
You gettin’ this, dumbo?
Yeah. I think this scene
is over. Yup.
Camera still on?
Oh, crap.
Turn it off, will ya?
Pete.
Lieutenant nun
leads the troops.
Wait.
This is it.
Movie sponsored
by the plaid council.
Plaid--it’s what’s
for dinner.
[Laughs]
Okay. Everyone
gets one juice box.
But that’s all.
I made a memorial
to your pee stain.
Let’s go.
Plaid avengers ho!
Serving 19.
Who has 19?
Oh, suddenly he’s like
mr. Flashlight.
[Laughs]
My god. I’ve found
the beginning of the movie.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
"Come this way."
We get it. Yeah.
There’s seven dwarves
comin’ right at us.
That’s the most complicated
trombone in the world.
Thanks for coming down
into my wine cellar with me,
guys.
I get scared.
See, I could point out
that this isn’t the future
and it’s not a war,
but you know me.
I don’t like to complain.
Not you.
No.
Not me.
[Laughs]
Lighting budget ran out,
but they just
keep on a-filmin’.
They’re hunting ed norton.
♪ N b c ♪
Why’d dale have to bring
his ironing board?
Viva le resistance.
Wow. Dinosaur’s got
a 10k back there.
Oh, by the way,
the wall you’re seeing
wasn’t the train
from the earlier scene.
So don’t even
think about it.
"Bong bong"
you know, I hope they
do the "bong bong" sound again,
mike.
You know,
I hope they never stop.
Yeah. I wish I had a huge
bong bong right now.
[Laughter]
What’s that light
supposed to be?
Is god outside?
Go.
Go here.
Come on.
Go.
Come on and go.
Go more.
And then drive.
Go. Go.
♪ Can you hear them
they’re talkin’ ’bout us ♪
♪ tellin’ lies ♪
Go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go. Go.
Now stay.
Hooray. We did an awesome job
of walking down the hall.
Whoo.
Come on.
Another high five.
We made it five more feet
down the hall. Whoo.
Jack johnson’s back
and he’s fightin’
with a gun this time.
And you brought along
the raccoon trap. Why?
Now, when foghorn leghorn
comes around the corner,
he’s ours.
[Growling]
I only wish my arms
were long enough to hold you.
So I said,
"up your jurassic, pal."
[Laughter]
That’s a good one.
[Laughs]
Well, I should get home.
Hey, stan.
Can you recommend
a good place to get
an exploding collar fixed?
Now serving nine.
We found ’em.
Down there.
It’s a fixx video
without the music.
Mm. Good.
Robert-claire
guards his comrades.
♪ Alouette
gentille alouette ♪
♪ alouette
je te plumerai ♪
♪ ya pa pa pa
pa pa pa ♪
So, according to the bells
it’s 97 o’clock.
[Sighs]
Well, do you wanna,
I don’t know...
High-five me?
We have to draw them
out of there.
I know.
Can I use the flashlight?
Are you scared?
Yeah.
But the sauna’s
helping me relax.
Greater love hath no man,
remember?
I do.
He’s an apprentice
bryan brown.
You really got a clean shave
this morning.
By the way,
I asked sister bertrille
to give us air support
against the dinosaurs.
Let’s do this thing.
Wow. Right here?
I mean, right now?
I--i--i mean,
I wanted to, but wow.
Introducing new,
faster seconds.
[Laughs]
Oh, sure.
Dss is easy to install.
Can’t get that stupid pigeon
out of there.
I, uh--i need the key
to the chest freezer.
Ah, [laughs]
Tick tick tick,
little bomby.
Tick tick tick. Remember?
May you road be paved
with sausages.
♪ Why don’t you ask him ♪
♪ if he’s going to stay ♪
♪ why don’t you ask him ♪
♪ if he’s going away ♪
♪ hmm hmm hmm
tusk ♪
♪ don’t say that
ya love me ♪
[Laughs]
Things.
Come on.
Over here.
We’re getting extinct.
Do you mind?
Should just wait until their
scales turn into feathers
and then pluck ’em.
[Growling]
Hi.
Good to see you again.
I’m on flashlight.
Help!
I’m just gonna throw
a couple of bales of hay
while i’m here.
♪ Doo doo doo
doo doo ♪
And in this corner...
[Laughs]
♪ Doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo ♪
Uh-huh.
As previously seen.
[Screams]
No!
Dinosaur super-sized it.
Oh, the ice fishing’s
bad here.
Wee.
So, they heaved
a mic stand at him.
[Laughs]
Ain’t it funny
how time slips away?
Stupid mammals.
Conroy!
Come on.
They’re right behind us.
We gotta go.
They need more time.
I need to buy them more time.
Take her. Take her.
[Scoffs]
Bonjour.
Aw, [...]
Boy,
dressing like che guevara
didn’t help at all.
His careful plan involving
putting on a beret
and rushing at the dinosaur
with a boy scout knife.
It would have been
much more effective
to get him into a bathtub
and then drop a hair dryer
into the water.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
The awesome power
of a 60 watt bulb.
Yeah.
Now back to drug dealin’.
Whoo.
Hmm?
I got better.
Careful.
That chin might go off.
Go get ’em, sister.
Good luck now.
Time for a little
chin music.
Ow.
Z’don’t.
Am I a hippie?
[Laughs]
Aah!
Raah reeh raah!
I’m fretting.
See audience?
Oh, the doctor says
he has to wear
his glaucoma test forever.
Got ya.
Uh, his chin’s
off balance.
Ooh.
Big zit.
Let’s go be on fame.
♪ Doo doo doo
doo doo doo ♪
It’s a 5k spaz run.
Slower.
Jog lightly
out of danger.
♪ Dinosaurs
are chasin’ us ♪
You forgot
your backpack--aah!
You guys get
dinosaur intestines
all over you too?
Hi.
I’m a director.
Please enjoy this small,
inaccurate model
of what we’d like to imply
just happened.
Thank you.
Four days ago
a fire fell from the sky...
Mm-hmm.
And I thought
everything it brought
would just extinguish
and burn away.
I’m kinda dumb.
Now, for all the questions
and doubts I had,
everything seems so clear.
Hi, sister chuck.
I think the one
in the black likes me.
In the name of the father,
the son, and the holy spirit.
Amen.
Father oliver platt.
Dear sister.
Do you now want to commit
to this bond
of perpetual devotion?
Yes I will.
Can I try for a week?
Do you want to strive
for the perfect love of god
and of your neighbor,
following the spirit
of the gospel?
Yeah.
I guess.
Yes. I will.
By the grace
of the holy spirit,
do you want to generously
spend your whole life
in the service
of god’s people?
[Laughs]
You think
she’s gonna do it?
No way, man.
By the grace
of the holy spirit,
do you want to spend
your whole life
in the service
of god’s people?
Oh, and god’s car.
You’ll have to take care
of that too.
When he was a future slave
he worked in the hair gel mines.
[Sighs]
Years of expensive
nun training
just wasted.
Yes. I wi--
it’s super pope.
[Laughs]
If the lutherans
create a cyborg.
It’s liberation theology
versus opus dei.
I open my mouth at you.
My shirt was knocked off.
It was knocked off.
I swear.
Wow. He’s got the longest
butt crack i’ve ever seen.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. Call the reconstructive
urologist.
Look at that beautiful
stained glass window.
They must have had
a loser bishop
to get a basilica
like this.
I think it’s just
the arby’s employee chapel.
You still think
I took my shirt off.
Don’t you?
Better one.
Better two.
I just wanna see
where he’s gonna go with this.
I’m just gonna stand here
and watch.
Oh. I see.
Well, ouch, then.
Huh.
Future sacred statuary hater.
Here.
Well,
now his chest is healed.
Oh, well,
now it’s not.
now it is again.
Sorry.
Oh, now it’s not.
My fault.
Oh, now it’s not again.
It is. It’s not.
Oh.
Did I make my point,
though?
Eloquently.
Oh.
[Beeping]
Rip taylor
as the android.
Huh?
THE MOVIE THAT DELIVERS
MORE "HUHs" PER SECOND.
I tried to light
a votive candle for my grandma
and it got out of control.
This is a weird p.S.A.
For the catholic church.
Oh, thanks.
Great nun ceremony.
Uh, is this allowed
in the chapel?
The ambulance is here.
Ambulance.
So much to learn.
So much.
Oh, shh.
You’re gonna be all right.
Okay?
I learn from you.
Mm-hmm.
I want...
To play with a flashlight.
Greater love
has no man than this.
I wanna be that man.
Jesus was a kickboxer,
right?
You are.
You ask me...
If there’s a heaven
out there.
Shh.
I don’t wanna know.
I’m an agnostic.
I know.
Four days ago,
a fire fell from the sky.
I know.
Everything he wanted
was everything I needed.
So, neither of us
actually got anything.
[Phone ringing]
Hill street rehab.
How can I help you?
Hello.
I’m a runaway.
I’m all alone.
Can you help me please?
Score.
Nice counselor picture.
Now that passion
for living and giving life
burns deeply and forever
in my heart.
Okay. You guys.
Hey. Listen.
I got something really cool
I wanna show you.
Just--just wait right here.
Okay?
Um, okay.
Just wait right there.
So, he ditched us.
Apparently.
Hmm.
No. It’s really,
really cool.
Just hang on.
Hey. Hey, servo.
Where’s that thing of yours?
What thing?
Uh, you know, could you
step it up a bit, mike?
The actors
have really stupid names.
Just a minute.
Hey, crow.
Look.
Just "adash," please.
[Laughs]
What?
Well,
i’m just makin’ fun of the--
well, don’t.
Okay.
Here we go.
Here we go what?
Now, watch.
Watch.
[Growling]
Uh, mike?
Why are you growling?
It’s a giant dinosaur.
See?
I don’t get you,
mike.
It’s--it’s
forced perspective.
By being over here,
I can make this
toy dinosaur look huge.
Over where?
Oh, oh, hell.
There you are.
What are you doing
with my toy?
I--i’m demonstrating
forced perspective.
Oh,
how nice for you.
don’t be so sardonic.
It’s neat. Look.
You can bite your head--
okay, mike.
Let’s humor you.
It is neat.
Well,
sure it is.
And you can do it with
all kinds of things.
Why, uh, heck.
If you wanted, you could
make a giant wrench.
Look.
Look out, you two.
Ahh!
I’m a giant wrench. Aah!
So it’s a wrench.
Only really big.
Big wrench.
Yeah.
And look.
Uh, what was once
an ordinary set
of pinking shears
becomes
a sort of a crocodile.
[Laughs]
Clever.
Crocodile.
Yeah.
Isn’t that neat?
And look.
You know your
little toy rabbit?
Yeah?
It becomes the star
of night of the lepus.
Mike,
what’s all this really about?
Come on. This is because joel
stopped by recently,
isn’t it?
It’s joel,
right?
No. No.
Wait. Wait wait.
There’s more.
With forced perspective this
"precious moments" figurine
looms as large
as the statue of liberty.
You know,
he has a point, crow.
No, no, no, no.
He has no point.
Don’t encourage him.
Hey, and,
and children, look.
Here comes gamera.
Gamera is friend
to all children.
Have you seen
his medication?
No i--i think
he’s off it again.
Oh, no.
And finally...
Servo’s chew toy
looks just like
the satellite of love.
See?
Huh.
Well, hey.
Hey there ya go.
That’s the spirit,
servo.
You’ve made yourself into
"giant servo--
destroyer of whole cities."
Uh, mike?
Actually i’m still over here.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
There you are.
What, uh--
[roars]
Aah! Aah!
It--it’s a giant servo!
Run!
Help!
It’s a giant servo!
Oh, no!
A horrible giant servo!
Run for your life,
mike!
Head for the hills,
Run!
Run, mike!
[Laughter]
That’s it,
you poor sap.
Whoo,
we stuck him bad.
Oh, man.
Good one, tom.
Uh, how did you manage
the effect so well?
[Laughs]
Well, what do you mean?
I mean, how do you operate
the other head while
you sit there?
You know, I was just about
to ask you the same question.
Oh. You were.
[Roars]
Okay. Back away
very slowly and run!
[Screams]
Ow.
Hi. It’s me.
Tom servo.
Don’t try to figure it out.
Hell, I got at least
a dozen of me.
Uh, good night.
[Laughs]
[Laughter]
Grrr.
It’s fun.
Hi, guys.
Huh.
Notice anything?
Uh-huh.
Sure, mike.
I’m wearing a funny chin.
Oh, look.
Just stop, would ya?
Geez.
But I can’t.
It’s big and it’s funny.
♪ I have a big chin
I have a big chin ♪
Don’t you even care
how insulting you are
to the thousands
of people out there
who have big,
prosthetic, foam chins?
Hmm.
Nope.
You know why?
’cause I have a big chin.
Ho ho ho ho.
It’s big.
Sorry, everyone.
Uh, pearl’s calling,
you insensitive cow.
Oh.
Watch this.
[Groans]
Big chin.
Say.
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
Results show this film
causes bizarre behavior
without the use
of hallucinogens.
Brain guy,
send this report
to the institute.
I don’t follow you,
my friend.
No way.
We’re going on the road.
Too true,
fair lady.
Our sound is tight,
ya know?
Mellow?
Bobo’s lyrics
are pure poetry, man.
Yes. We’re opening
the moby grape reunion tour
in santa cruz.
Oh.
You are.
Hmm.
How nice.
Well, I have some
parting gifts for both of you.
These are handmade
love necklaces
so’s you both have
something special
to remember me by.
Pearl, you are too, too solid
for this world, man.
Bobo.
Hit me with some lyric.
♪ Like a dog in the sand ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
[Explosions]
Now they’re
eight miles high.